chatrwireless.com 2014-10-07

# chatr wireless - Privacy Policy

1.

This policy applies to chatr wireless which is referred to hereafter as chatr or chatr wireless. At chatr wireless, the security and integrity of our customers' personal information is important to us. We take every reasonable measure necessary to protect the privacy of our customers while providing the high level communication services they expect.

2.

chatr's privacy practices are in accordance with all federal and provincial laws and regulations. We are compliant with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and where applicable with the privacy rules established by the Canadian Radio-television and Telecommunications Commission (CRTC).

3.

chatr wireless has in place privacy and security practices to safeguard our customers' personal information. These practices are reviewed, and if necessary revised, on a regular basis. Additionally, chatr's employees receive privacy training and must comply with chatr's privacy practices as a condition of employment.

4.

Personal information collected by chatr wireless may include such information as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit and financial information, birth date and any recorded complaints.

5.

At chatr, we collect customer information for one or more of the following purposes:

To provide a positive customer experience, and deliver, bill for, and collect payment for products and services;

To understand customer requirements and make information available regarding products and services offered by chatr wireless and its agents, dealers and related companies;

To manage and develop chatr wireless business and operations;

To meet legal and regulatory requirements; and

To obtain credit information or provide it to others.

6.

chatr wireless does not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. chatr wireless retains personal information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

7.

chatr wireless informs customers of the existence, use and disclosure of their personal information upon request and gives them access to their information.

8.

chatr wireless ensures that customer information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Customers can challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and request amendments as appropriate.

9.

chatr wireless shares information with its affiliates, agents and authorized dealers, in order to offer customers products and services that they may find attractive. Notices on sharing information are contained on Chatr’s invoice and on chatr.com.

10.

chatr's customers may have their names removed from our telephone, mail or email marketing lists. We use these lists to inform customers of relevant products, services and special offers that may be of benefit to them. If customers do not want to be marketed with these products and services, they can contact Chatr Wireless directly at 1-800-485-9745.

11.

A senior company officer has been appointed as the Privacy Officer at chatr wireless . The Privacy Officer is accountable for all personal information at chatr wireless . You may contact the Privacy Officer at:

| By Mail| Chief Privacy Officer  
---|---  
 | chatr wireless  
 | 333 Bloor Street East  
 | Toronto, Ontario  
 | M4W 1G9  

12.

Customers that wish to:

obtain more information about chatr wireless Commitment to Privacy;

access, or obtain more information about their personal information held by chatr wireless ; or

make a privacy-related complaint;

may contact a chatr wireless customer service representative who, if necessary, will refer the customer to the chatr wireless Privacy Officer.

13.

The Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada oversees chatr's personal information handling practices. If your privacy concerns are not addressed to your satisfaction by chatr wireless you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada for further guidance:
